http://www.gladesprings.com/privacy-policy.html

Toggle navigationBook NowHomeRoomsPackagesMeetingsAdventures & ActivitiesCOVID SafetyDiningOrder AmenitiesThanksgiving To-GoAbout UsContact UsDirectionsGolfSpa OrangeSkiFamily ReunionsWeddingsSummit Bechtel ReserveGolf & Country ClubReal EstateCareersPrivacy PolicyRoomsPackagesMeetingsAdventures & ActivitiesCOVID SafetyDiningOrder AmenitiesThanksgiving To-GoAbout UsContact UsDirectionsGolfSpa OrangeSkiFamily ReunionsWeddingsSummit Bechtel ReserveGolf & Country ClubReal EstateCareersPrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThe Resort at Glade SpringsPlease read fully.This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.The Resort at Glade Springs does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information that is submitted through forms on this website, our marketing campaigns, or lead forms. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. Your information is used to respond to submitted requests for price quotes, to process transactions and reservations, provide meeting and event information, or to send periodic promotional emails to the individuals completing such forms.Do we use 'cookies'?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We use cookies to deliver advertisements across the Internet and content relevant to your interests by collecting and maintaining information based on your web surfing activity when you are visiting our website. We may also use cookies to provide general internal and customer analytics.We use cookies to:Understand and save user's preferences for future visits and deliver advertisements across the Internet. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.If users disable cookies in their browser:If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly. You may have to log in every time you load The Resort at Glade Springs.Third-party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.By using our site, you consent to our website privacy policy. Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted to this page.
The Resort at Glade Springs 255 Resort Dr, Daniels, WV, 25832, United States DirectionsSocial MediaFacebook Google+ Instagram Tripadvisor Twitter YouTube
All rights reserved Powered by Canvas
